SALEM EZZ 4700 Westgrove st apt. 805 Raleigh, NC 27606 919-260-5009 salem.ezz@gmail.com

PROFILE

My background is in both design and communications. I ran a small marketing and production firm for creatives and small businesses called Trickle Media for several years with a few other multimedia artists. I have been fully versed in Word Press, the Adobe Creative Suite and various other digital workstations for more than 7 years. Currently I am researching Agile and UI/UXphilosophies.

EDUCATION AND CERTIFICATIONS

University of North Carolina | Chapel Hill, NC | Certificate In Coding, 2018

Central Carolina Community Collage | Pittsboro, NC | Arts Associates, 2015

Central Carolina Community Collage | Pittsboro, NC | Certificate in Sustainable Ag, 2013

EXPERIENCE

TRICKLE MEDIA | OWNER/MULTIMEDIA ARTIST | CHAPEL HILL, NC | AUG. 2013 - PRESENT

Provide multimedia services to local artists and businesses by both freelance and management under an entity. Media Services including web design, graphic design, print, video, and marketing.

Sales Representative | Fifth Season Gardening Co | Raleigh, NC | Aug. 2015 - Mar. 2016

Manage nutrient and pH levels in demo displays. Fix broken equipment, spray pesticides, and propagate plants for display. Sell indoor growing equipment to customers.

PR Intern | Seven Waves Corp | Chapel Hill, NC | Apr. 2013 - Sept. 2013

Write press releases for new solar farm deals. Aggregate contacts for public relations list. Manage

SHOWROOM ASSISTANT | CAT'S CRADLE | CARRBORO, NC | SEPT. 2014 - MAR. 2016

Admit attendees to events. Help plan and organize events. Manage and distribute printed collateral.

SKILLS

Graphic Design, 2D/3D Animation, Original Music Production, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery, Bootstrap, Express.js, React.js, Node.js, Database Theory, MongoDB, MySQL, Git, C++